<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Red on Decanted</title>
    <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/categories/red/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Red on Decanted</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/categories/red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beaujolais Villages Louis Jadot</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0010-beaujolais-villages-louis-jadot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0010-beaujolais-villages-louis-jadot/</guid>
      <description> This is one of my favorite every-day drinkers. It&amp;rsquo;s super affordable, readily-available, and lovely. This is a go-to for me in the summer time. Goes great with roast chicken or pork. It&amp;rsquo;s fresh taste and bright acidity is a great compliment to the roasted meat.
Tasting Notes  Medium ruby in color Initial aromas of red fruit—raspberries, cherry, cranberry Secondary aroma of vanilla and yeast Medium-minus body Dry Bright acidity Low tannin Medium alcohol Medium-minus lenght on the finish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Côtes Du Rhône Vidal-Fleury</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0008-vidal-fleury-cotes-du-rhone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0008-vidal-fleury-cotes-du-rhone/</guid>
      <description> Nothing too special about this wine. It&amp;rsquo;s a cheap GSM blend. This was my first real experience of a Côte Du Rhône. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t great, but definitely got me interested in the region. I&amp;rsquo;v got a few bottles from this region on my wishlist.
Tasting Notes  Medium-dark ruby in color Lost of dark fruit—blackberry, Plumb, raspberry Jammy, overripe, cooked fruit flavors (Maybe a hot vintage) A hint of rubber/plastic Dry, not much residual sugar Medium-plus body Medium-plus acidity almost juicy Medium-plus alcohol Light presence of tannin, no signs of oak  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chateau du Bousquet</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0006-chateau-du-bousquet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0006-chateau-du-bousquet/</guid>
      <description> This was one of the first Bordeauxs I&amp;rsquo;ve every tried. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t great, but a decent introducion to this style. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t seek this one out again.
Tasting Notes  Dark ruby with hints of brown arond the edges Primary aroma of dark red fruit—cranberry, and jam Some vegital aromoas of tomato and earth Clove and vanilla Medium-minus body High acidity Medium-minus tannin Medium finish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casillera del Diablo Carménerè</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0005-casillera-del-diablo-carmenere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0005-casillera-del-diablo-carmenere/</guid>
      <description> Pretty great value at $12 a bottle. I would stock up on this as it would age pretty well for at least a while, and it would be great to have on hand to go with a nice and simple grilled steak.
Tasting Notes  Dark ruby in color Intitial aroma of black cherry, black berry, currant Some dried cherry, vanilla spice, and leather Medium body Medium-minus acidity Medium-minus tannin on the back of the tongue Some eucalyptus and resin on the palate Medium finish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viña Bujanda Rioja</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0004-vina-bujanda-rioja/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0004-vina-bujanda-rioja/</guid>
      <description> This wine was OK but nothing to get too excited about. I&amp;rsquo;d be interested to taste this vintage again in a year or too once it&amp;rsquo;s had a chance to mellow out.
Tasting Notes  100% Tempranillo Dark ruby in color Black cherry, currants, vegetal, bell pepper Some oaky spiciness, with some piney resinous qualities Medium-plus tannin Medium-plus body  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ibericos Riojoa</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0003-ibericos-rioja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0003-ibericos-rioja/</guid>
      <description> I loved this wine. Would go great with some salty snacks, or cured meats.
Tasting Notes  Dark ruby in color Black cherry, vegetal aromas Oaky vanilla secondary aromas and taste Some spice/peppery notes Medium tannin that come on strong at the back of the tongue I got a little bit of green flower, like dandelion in the finish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hedgeline Vinyards Pinot Noir</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0002-hedgeline-pinot-noir/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0002-hedgeline-pinot-noir/</guid>
      <description> This wine is actually made in California by Winepress Vintners (probably part of a big conglomerate), but it is made from Oregon Pinot Noir grapes. This was a really enjoyable and affordable wine and I would buy again for sure.
Tasting Notes  Light ruby in color with tints of brown around the edges Lots of fresh red fruit and floral aromas Light body Caramel and almond notes in the finish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creekbend Noir</title>
      <link>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0001-creekbend-noir/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://levimcg.github.io/decanted/notes/0001-creekbend-noir/</guid>
      <description> I love this wine. It&amp;rsquo;s a personal favorite of my wife&amp;rsquo;s and mine. The grapes are grown about 10 miles from where we live at Creekbend Vinyard in Elletseville, Indiana. This is my go to bottle of to gift to friends and family that aren&amp;rsquo;t already wine drinkers due to how approachable and easy-drinking it is.
Tasting Notes  52% Corot, 48% Marechal Foch grapes Dried Fruit, Cherry, Raisins Medium body High fruity and juicy acidity  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>